Oh, the people are heartbroken!
(Sheldon:)I can't take this away
from the world!
Fun with Flags is back!
(Leonard:)Congratulations.
Let's celebrate!
(cork pops)
(Sheldon:)Sheldon,
that wasn't for you!
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, I'm not going
to drink it.
(Sheldon:)I just wanted to hear the pop.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I knew it was coming.
Still scary.
(Sheldon:)LeVar Burton?
LeVar Burton!
(LeVar:)Ugh. What are you doing here?
(Sheldon:)You told me not to call,
(Sheldon:)and I didn't know how else
to give you the good news.
(Sheldon:)Fun with Flags is back, and
you can be in the next episode.
(LeVar:)Wil Wheaton said, get a gate.
(LeVar:)I don't know why
I didn't get a gate.
You...
(Sheldon:)At least listen
to the premise.
(Sheldon:)Since you were born
in Germany,
(Sheldon:)I thought we could talk
about German flags.
How do you feel about
dressing up like a swastika?